Guide to the Jack Anderson papers, 1930-2004 MS2001
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Research files, 1975; 1959-2000; MS2001 Series 4; 59.5 Linear Feet 113 document boxes, 3 flat boxes
  - General, 1982-1983
    - Article Research, 1969; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 442, Folder 2)
    - Article Research, 1980-1981; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 279, Folder 1)
    - Article Research, 1984-1985; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 279, Folder 2)
    - Article Research, 1974; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 279, Folder 3)
    - Article Research, 1972; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 279, Folder 4)
    - Article Research by George Clifford, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 279, Folder 5)
    - Article Research - Military, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 279, Folder 6)
    - Article research, unspecified [1 of 2], 1988; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 442, Folder 3)
    - Article research, unspecified [2 of 2], undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 442, Folder 4)
    - Asher, Robert, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 279, Folder 7)
    - Ashley, Thomas, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 431, Folder 5)
    - Ashmore, Robert T., 1970; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 431, Folder 6)
    - Aspinall, Wayne, 1965; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 431, Folder 7)
    - Associated Milk Producers, Inc., 1967-1969; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 280, Folder 1)
    - Assorted notes and correspondence re: congressmen, 1967-1969; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 433, Folder 23)
    - Atomic Energy Commission, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 280, Folder 2)
    - Atomic Blast Danger, 1969-1975; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 280, Folder 3)
    - Aujezsky disease, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 280, Folder 4)
    - Auto industry, 1987; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 280, Folder 5)
    - Aviation safety, 1963-1965; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 280, Folder 6)
    - AWACS, 1973; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box R1, Folder 5, Box 280, Folder 7)
    - Bader, Lewis, 1968; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 280, Folder 8)
    - Bahamas, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 280, Folder 9, Box R1, Folder 6)
    - Baird, William R., 1963-1966; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 280, Folder 10)
    - Baird, Zoe, 1964-1965; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 280, Folder 11)
    - Baker, Bobby [1 of 2], undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 280, Folder 12)
    - Baker, Bobby [2 of 2], 1987; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 281, Folder 1)
    - Baker, Howard, 1968; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 431, Folder 8)
    - Baldridge, Malcolm, 1984-1985; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 281, Folder 2)
    - Baldwin, Phillip, 1966-1974; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 281, Folder 3)
    - Bank supervision, 1963-1965; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 281, Folder 4)
    - Bankers and banking, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 281, Folder 5)
    - Banking, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 281, Folder 6)
    - Bankruptcy, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 281, Folder 7)
    - Bass, Ross, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 281, Folder 8)
    - Bayh, Birch [1 of 2], 1966; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 281, Folder 9)
    - Bayh, Birch [2 of 2], undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 431, Folder 9)
    - Beatles, 1979; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 281, Folder 10)
    - Belcher, Page, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 431, Folder 10)
    - Bell, Griffin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 281, Folder 11)
    - Bennett, Charles, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 431, Folder 11)
    - Bennett, Robert, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 281, Folder 12)
    - Bennett, Wallace, 2004; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 431, Folder 12)
    - Berry, E.Y., undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 431, Folder 13)
    - Best MGR columns, 1971; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 281, Folder 13)
    - Bible, Alan, 1974; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 431, Folder 14)
    - Bicentennial Commission, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 281, Folder 14)
    - Bicentennial contest, 1966; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 281, Folder 15)
    - Blatnik, John, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 431, Folder 15)
    - Boggs, Hale, 1975; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 281, Folder 16)
    - Boggs, J. Caleb, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 431, Folder 16)
    - Bohling, Curt, 1975; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 281, Folder 17)
    - Bolling, Richard, 1983; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 431, Folder 17)
    - Boorstin, Daniel, 1974; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 281, Folder 18)
    - Bouvia, Elizabeth, 1963; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 281, Folder 19)
    - Brasco, Frank, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 281, Folder 20)
    - Brinkley, David, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 282, Folder 1)
    - Brezhnev, Leonid, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 431, Folder 18)
    - Brock, William E., undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 431, Folder 19)
    - Brooks, Jack, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 431, Folder 20)
    - Brown, George E., Jr., 1978; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 431, Folder 21)
    - Broyhill, Joel, 1971; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 431, Folder 22)
    - Brzezinski, Zbigniew, 1983; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box R1, Folder 7, Box 282, Folder 2)
    - Buckley, James, 1986; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 282, Folder 3)
    - Budget, 1963-1965; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 282, Folder 4, Box R1, Folder 8)
    - Budget, 1968; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box R1, Folder 9, Box 282, Folder 5)
    - Bundy, McGeorge - correspondence, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 282, Folder 6)
    - Burden v. Irving Trust Co., 1969; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 282, Folder 7, Box R1, Folder 10)
    - Burdick, Quentin, 1966-1969; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 431, Folder 23)
    - Bureau of Indian Affairs, 1969-1975; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 282, Folder 8)
    - Bureaucracy, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 282, Folder 9)
    - Burger, Warren, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 282, Folder 10)
    - Burleson, Omar, 1980-1987; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 431, Folder 24)
    - Burton, 1971; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 282, Folder 11)
    - Bush, George H. W., 1988; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 282, Folder 12)
    - Busing, 1965; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 282, Folder 13)
    - The Buying of America, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 282, Folder 14)
    - Byrd, Harry, 1974; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 282, Folder 15)
    - Cabell, Earle, 1987; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 431, Folder 25)
    - California notaries, 1971; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 282, Folder 16)
    - California Trial Lawyers Association, 1970-1979; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 282, Folder 17)
    - Calley, William L., Jr., 1982; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box R1, Folder 11, Box 282, Folder 18)
    - Cambodia, 1956-1968; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 282, Folder 19)
    - Camp David Agreement, 1968; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 282, Folder 20)
    - Campaign contributions, 1966-1974; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 282, Folder 21)
    - Campaign financing, 1971-1973; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 283, Folder 1)
    - Campaign spending, 1963; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 283, Folder 2)
    - Campaign strategies, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 283, Folder 3)
    - Canadian trade, 1967-1975; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 283, Folder 4)
    - Canal zone, 1968-1976; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 283, Folder 5)
    - Cancer, 2000; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 283, Folder 6)
    - Candidate biographies, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 283, Folder 7)
    - Cannon, Grant, 1986; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 283, Folder 8)
    - Cannon, Howard, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 431, Folder 26)
    - Cannon, Ted, 1961-1962; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 283, Folder 9)
    - Capital Hill philandering, 1968; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 283, Folder 10, Box R2, Folder 1)
    - Capital Vending Co., 1966; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 283, Folder 11)
    - Carmichael, Stokely, 1977-1980; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 283, Folder 12)
    - Carpenter, Elizabeth, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 283, Folder 13)
    - Carter, Billy, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 283, Folder 14)
    - Carter, Jimmy, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 283, Folder 15)
    - Carto, Willis, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 283, Folder 16)
    - Case, Clifford, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 431, Folder 27)
    - Casey, Bob, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 431, Folder 28)
    - Casey, General George, Sr., 1990; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 283, Folder 17)
    - Casey, William, Sr., 1961; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box R2, Folder 2, Box 283, Folder 18)
    - Casolaro, Danny, 1969; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 283, Folder 19)
    - Castro, Fidel, 1971-1972; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 283, Folder 20)
    - Caudle, T. Lamar, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 283, Folder 21)
    - CBS, 1963-1970; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 284, Folder 1)
    - Celler, Emanuel, 1983-1984; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 431, Folder 29)
    - Census data, 1970; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 284, Folder 2)
    - Central America, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 284, Folder 3, Box R2)
    - Central Southwest Oil Corporation, 1969; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 284, Folder 4)
    - Chamberlain, Charles, 1969; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 431, Folder 30)
    - Chappaquiddick - Ted Kennedy [1 of 2], Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 284, Folder 5)
    - Chappaquiddick - Ted Kennedy [2 of 2], Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 284, Folder 6)
    - Chemical and biological weapons, 1970; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 284, Folder 7)
    - Chevron, 1989; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 284, Folder 8)
    - Chicago Seven, 1968-1973; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 284, Folder 9)
    - Chiefs of police, 1972-1973; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 284, Folder 10)
    - Children, 1963-1966; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 284, Folder 11)
    - Chile, 1960-1969; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 284, Folder 12)
    - China [1 of 2], 1978-1979; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 284, Folder 13)
    - China [2 of 2], 2002; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 284, Folder 14)
    - China, 1970-1971; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 285, Folder 1, Box R2, Folder 6)
    - China Reform Monitor, 1987; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 285, Folder 2)
    - Chotiner, Murray, 1975; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 285, Folder 3)
    - Chrysler, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 285, Folder 4)
    - Church Committee - U.S. Senate, 1980-1981; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 285, Folder 5)
    - Church, Frank, 1954-1976; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 285, Folder 6)
    - CIA, 1954-1976; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 285, Folder 7, Box R2)
    - CIA [1 of 2], 1963; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 285, Folder 8)
    - CIA [2 of 2], 1971; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 285, Folder 9)
    - CIA Bugging, 1988; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 285, Folder 10, Box R2, Folder 8)
    - CIA and State Department intelligence documents, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 285, Folder 11, Box R2, Folder 9)
    - Ciosek, William, 1968; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 285, Folder 12)
    - Citizens Against Government Waste, 1970; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 285, Folder 13)
    - Citizens Committee for Buchanan, 1966-1969; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 285, Folder 14)
    - Civil Aeronautics Board, 1980; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 285, Folder 15)
    - Civil Rights, 1967; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 285, Folder 16)
    - Civiletti, Benjamin, 1967; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 286, Folder 1)
    - Clark, Joseph, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 286, Folder 2)
    - Clark, Ramsey [1 of 2], 1978; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 286, Folder 3)
    - Clark, Ramsey [2 of 2], undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 431, Folder 31)
    - Clark Tanklines Company, 1966; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 286, Folder 4)
    - Cleveland, James C., 1998; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 431, Folder 32)
    - Clifford, Clark, 1993-1996; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 286, Folder 5)
    - Clinton, Bill, 1995-1997; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 286, Folder 6)
    - Clinton, Bill - FBI, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 286, Folder 7)
    - Clinton, Bill - fundraising, 1968; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 286, Folder 8)
    - Clintons' tax returns, 1970-1974; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 286, Folder 9)
    - Coal, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 286, Folder 10)
    - Coast Guard, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 286, Folder 11)
    - Cohn, Roy, 1975; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 431, Folder 34)
    - Cohen, Sheldon, 1975; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 431, Folder 33)
    - Colby, DCI, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 286, Folder 12)
    - Colby, William, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 286, Folder 13)
    - Collins, James, 1967-1969; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 286, Folder 14)
    - Colson, Charles, 1991; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 286, Folder 15)
    - Column leads, 1962; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 286, Folder 16)
    - Commercial Drivers License, 1968-1975; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 286, Folder 17)
    - Committee for Economic Growth, 1967-1976; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 286, Folder 18)
    - Committee on Foreign Relations, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 286, Folder 19)
    - Communism, 1984; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 286, Folder 20)
    - Communist propaganda, 1959-1965; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 286, Folder 21)
    - Computers, 1959-1965; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 286, Folder 22)
    - Conflicts of interest [1 of 2], 1960-1973; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 286, Folder 23)
    - Conflicts of interest [2 of 2], 1960-1973; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 286, Folder 24)
    - Congress [1 of 4], 1960-1973; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 287, Folder 1)
    - Congress [2 of 4], 1960-1973; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 287, Folder 2)
    - Congress [3 of 4], 1950; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 287, Folder 3)
    - Congress [4 of 4], 1966; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 287, Folder 4)
    - Congressional immunity re: libel and slander, 1962-1964; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 442, Folder 5)
    - Congressional Record, 1971-1974; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 287, Folder 5)
    - Congressmen who front for foreign affairs, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 287, Folder 6)
    - Conspiracy arguments, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 288, Folder 1)
    - Constitution, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 288, Folder 2)
    - Constitutional law, 1978; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 288, Folder 3)
    - Consumer affairs, 1964; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 288, Folder 4)
    - Consumer information, 1981; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 288, Folder 5)
    - Consumer issues, 1967; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 288, Folder 6)
    - Consumer Product Safety Commission, 1995-1996; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 288, Folder 7)
    - Consumer protection, 1964-1965; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 288, Folder 8)
    - Consumption tax, 1964-1965; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 288, Folder 9)
    - Cooley, Harold - Sugar Act [1 of 2], 1972; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 288, Folder 10)
    - Cooley, Harold - Sugar Act [2 of 2], 1966; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 288, Folder 11)
    - Corporate executives, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 288, Folder 12)
    - Corso, Philip, 1964-1965; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 288, Folder 13)
    - Cosa Nostra, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 288, Folder 14)
    - Cotten, Richard, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 288, Folder 15)
    - Counterfeiting, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 288, Folder 16)
    - Counterfeiting - Russia, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 289, Folder 1)
    - Court scandals, 1973; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 289, Folder 2)
    - Covert action - CIA, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 289, Folder 3, Box R2, Folder 10)
    - Cox, Archibald, 1979; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 289, Folder 4)
    - Cramer, William, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 431, Folder 35)
    - Crane, Phil, 1982-1993; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 289, Folder 5)
    - Crime, 1973; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 289, Folder 6)
    - Croatia, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 289, Folder 7)
    - Cronkite, Walter, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 289, Folder 8)
    - Cuba, 1979; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box R2, Folder 11, Box 289, Folder 9)
    - Cuba, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 289, Folder 10)
    - Cuba/USSR relationship, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 289, Folder 11)
    - Curtis, Thomas B., undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 431, Folder 36)
    - Daddario, Emilio, 1965; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 431, Folder 37)
    - Day, James Edward, 1955-1964; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 431, Folder 38)
    - Death Valley, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 289, Folder 12)
    - Defectors, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 289, Folder 13)
    - Defense Department National Military Command Center, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box R2, Folder 12, Box 289, Folder 14)
    - Defense Intelligence Agency Fact Book [1 of 3], Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box R2, Folder 13, Box 289, Folder 15)
    - Defense Intelligence Agency Fact Book [2 of 3], Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box R2, Folder 14, Box 289, Folder 16)
    - Defense Intelligence Agency Fact Book [3 of 3], 1979; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box R3, Folder 1, Box 289, Folder 17)
    - Defense Intelligence Appraisal - USSR/Japan, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 289, Folder 18, Box R3, Folder 2)
    - Defense Intelligence Estimate - North Korea, 1974; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 289, Folder 19, Box R3, Folder 3)
    - Deficit spending, 1963-1996; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 290, Folder 1)
    - Dellums, Ron, 1968; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 290, Folder 2)
    - Demetracopoulos, Elias, 1972; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 290, Folder 3)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1962-1971; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 290, Folder 4)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1962-1963; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box R3, Folder 4, Box 290, Folder 5)
    - Democratic Party, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 290, Folder 6)
    - Democratic politics, 1971; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 290, Folder 7)
    - Department of Defense, 1971; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box R3, Folder 5, Box 290, Folder 8)
    - Department of Defense messages [1 of 2], 1978-1979; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box R3, Folder 6, Box 290, Folder 9)
    - Department of Defense messages [2 of 2], 1969-1975; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box R3, Folder 7, Box 290, Folder 10)
    - Department of Energy, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 290, Folder 11)
    - Department of Housing and Urban Development, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 290, Folder 12)
    - Department of the Interior, 1969; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 290, Folder 13)
    - Department of Justice, 1966-1968; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 290, Folder 14)
    - Department of Labor, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 290, Folder 15)
    - Department of the Navy, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 290, Folder 16)
    - Department of State telegrams [1 of 2], 1957; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box R3, Folder 8, Box 290, Folder 17)
    - Department of State telegrams [2 of 2], undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box R4, Folder 1, Box 290, Folder 18)
    - Deposition - Caesar L. Aiello, 1979; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 290, Folder 19)
    - Derwinski, Edward, 1971; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 431, Folder 39)
    - Devine, Frank, 1959-1962; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 458, Folder 6)
    - Diabetes, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 290, Folder 20)
    - Dillon, C. Douglas, 1961-1969; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 290, Folder 21)
    - Dingell, John, 1977; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 431, Folder 40)
    - Diplomats, 1962-1965; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 290, Folder 22)
    - Diplomat National Bank, 1971-1973; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 290, Folder 23)
    - Dirksen, Everett, 1977; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 290, Folder 24)
    - District of Columbia, 1965; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 291, Folder 1)
    - Divorce, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 291, Folder 2)
    - Dognapping, 1982; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 291, Folder 3)
    - Dominick, Peter, 1965-1967; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 431, Folder 41)
    - Dornan, Robert, 1970; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 291, Folder 4)
    - Douglas, Paul, 1968; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 291, Folder 5)
    - Douglas, William O., 1978; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 291, Folder 6)
    - Dowd, Thomas, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 291, Folder 7)
    - Drug Enforcement Administration, 1963; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box R4, Folder 2, Box 291, Folder 8)
    - Drug Enforcement Administration, 1971-1974; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 291, Folder 9)
    - Drug scandals, 1965-1966; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 291, Folder 10)
    - Drug trafficking, 1988; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 291, Folder 11)
    - Drugs and cigarettes, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 291, Folder 12)
    - Dukakis, Michael, 1972; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 291, Folder 13)
    - Dulski, Thaddeus, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 431, Folder 42)
    - Eagleton, Thomas, 1979; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 291, Folder 14)
    - Eastland, James, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 431, Folder 43)
    - East Timor, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 291, Folder 15)
    - Eavesdropping, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 291, Folder 16)
    - Edelsberg, Herman, 1973; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 291, Folder 17)
    - Education, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 291, Folder 18)
    - Ehrlichman, John, 1961; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 291, Folder 19)
    - Eichmann, Adolf, 1970; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 292, Folder 1)
    - Eichmann, Nicolas, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 292, Folder 2)
    - Eisenhower, David, 1981; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 292, Folder 3)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight, 1960-1967; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 431, Folder 44)
    - El Salvador, 1977; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box R4, Folder 3, Box 292, Folder 4)
    - Election process, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 292, Folder 5)
    - Electronic communications interception, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box R4, Folder 4, Box 292, Folder 6)
    - Ellender, Allen, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 431, Folder 45)
    - Ellis, Chuong Minh [1 of 3], undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 459, Folder 2)
    - Ellis, Chuong Minh [2 of 3], 1972; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 459, Folder 3)
    - Ellis, Chuong Minh [3 of 3], 2000; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 459, Folder 4)
    - Ellsberg, Daniel, 1965-1974; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 292, Folder 7)
    - Emergency preparedness, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 292, Folder 8)
    - Energy, 1966-1977; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 292, Folder 9)
    - Enron, 1980-1997; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 292, Folder 10)
    - Environment, 1973; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 292, Folder 11)
    - Environmental Protection Agency, 1953; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 292, Folder 12)
    - Ervin, Sam, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 292, Folder 13)
    - Espionage and security legislation, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 442, Folder 6)
    - E-Systems, Inc. [1 of 2], 1965-1966; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 292, Folder 14)
    - E-Systems, Inc. [2 of 2], 1997; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 293, Folder 1)
    - Ethics, 1978-1980; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 293, Folder 2)
    - Ethics reform, 1972-1973; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 293, Folder 3)
    - Ethiopia-Somalia conflict, 1966; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 293, Folder 4)
    - Evans, Dan, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 293, Folder 5)
    - Fair Campaign Practices Committee, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 293, Folder 6)
    - Falkland Islands crisis, 1973; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 293, Folder 7)
    - Family, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 293, Folder 8)
    - Fannin, Paul, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 293, Folder 9)
    - Farbstein, Leonard, 1978-1980; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 431, Folder 46)
    - Fascell, Dante, 1963-1976; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 431, Folder 47)
    - FBI, 1966-1973; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box R4, Folder 5, Box 293, Folder 10)
    - FBI, 1964-1969; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 293, Folder 11)
    - Federal Aviation Administration, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 293, Folder 12)
    - Federal Communications Commission, 1987-1990; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 293, Folder 13)
    - Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation, 1983; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 294, Folder 1)
    - Federal Home Loan Bank Board, 1968-1975; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 294, Folder 2)
    - Federal Reserve Board, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box R4, Folder 6, Box 294, Folder 3)
    - Federal Reserve Board, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 294, Folder 4)